<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RF Analyzer</string>
    <string name="about_screen_html"><![CDATA[
Copyright &#169; 2025 Dennis Mantz<br /><br />

<h1>About the App</h1>
RF Analyzer is an open source spectrum analyzer that lets you use you
SDR hardware together with an Android device. A detailed description
can be found in the <a href=https://demantz.github.io/RFAnalyzer/>
manual</a>.

Show the <a href=https://raw.githubusercontent.com/demantz/RFAnalyzer/master/changelog.txt>
changelog</a>.

<h1>Get Beta Releases</h1>
If you want to help the developer by testing beta releases you can
join the beta program on Google Play:<br />
<a href=https://play.google.com/apps/testing/com.mantz_it.rfanalyzer>
https://play.google.com/apps/testing/com.mantz_it.rfanalyzer</a>

<h1>Reporting Bugs</h1>
If you find any bugs or translation mistakes or if you want to request
a new feature please use the GitHub page of the project:<br />
<a href=https://github.com/demantz/RFAnalyzer/issues>
https://github.com/demantz/RFAnalyzer/issues</a>
<br /><br />
Alternatively you could write me an email to
<a href=mailto:rfanalyzerapp@gmail.com>rfanalyzerapp@gmail.com</a>.

<h1>License</h1>
<a href=http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl.html>GPL version 2 or higher</a>
<br /><br />
<small>This application is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public
License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
version 2 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
<br /><br />
This application is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU
General Public License for more details.
<br /><br />
You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public
License along with this library; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA 02110-1301 USA</small>
<br /><br />
Get the source code of the app here on <a href=https://github.com/demantz/RFAnalyzer>GitHub</a>!

<h1>Third Party Licenses</h1>
This app uses the following third party software modules:

<h2>pffft</h2>
Copyright (c) 2013  Julien Pommier ( pommier@modartt.com )
<br /><br />
Based on original fortran 77 code from FFTPACKv4 from NETLIB
(http://www.netlib.org/fftpack), authored by Dr Paul Swarztrauber
of NCAR, in 1985.
<br /><br />
As confirmed by the NCAR fftpack software curators, the following
FFTPACKv5 license applies to FFTPACKv4 sources. My changes are
released under the same terms.
<br /><br />
FFTPACK license:
<br /><br />
http://www.cisl.ucar.edu/css/software/fftpack5/ftpk.html
<br /><br />
Copyright (c) 2004 the University Corporation for Atmospheric
Research ("UCAR"). All rights reserved. Developed by NCARs
Computational and Information Systems Laboratory, UCAR,
www.cisl.ucar.edu.
<br /><br />
Redistribution and use of the Software in source and binary forms,
with or without modification, is permitted provided that the
following conditions are met:
<br /><br />
- Neither the names of NCARs Computational and Information Systems
Laboratory, the University Corporation for Atmospheric Research,
nor the names of its sponsors or contributors may be used to
endorse or promote products derived from this Software without
specific prior written permission.
<br /><br />
- Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
notices, this list of conditions, and the disclaimer below.
<br /><br />
- Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions, and the disclaimer below in the
documentation and/or other materials provided with the
distribution.
<br /><br />
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,
EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND
NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE CONTRIBUTORS OR COPYRIGHT
HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL,
EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN
ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN
CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS WITH THE
SOFTWARE.

<h2>hackrf_android (based on libhackrf)</h2>
This library is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of the License, or (at your option) any later version. http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl.html GPL version 2 or higher
<br /><br />
principal author of hackrf_android: Dennis Mantz <dennis.mantzgooglemail.com>
<br /><br />
principal author of libhackrf: Michael Ossmann <mikeossmann.com>
]]></string>

</resources>
